gunbot.net 2016-12-02

# Privacy Policy

PRIVACY POLICY

GENERAL  
Gunbot.net respects the privacy of all visitors to our website. In order to assist us in better serving our visitors, we may collect certain anonymous information automatically, and may require certain personal information. This Privacy Policy outlines the type of information that we may collect and the manner in which such information will be used. All efforts have been made to ensure the accuracy of the information provided herein, however Gunbot.net makes no warranties or representations as to the accuracy of the information supplied herein.

ANONYMOUS INFORMATION AUTOMATICALLY COLLECTED  
We may collect and use certain information about your use of this web site that does not personally identify you. This information includes your IP address and other standard information such as pages viewed, the date and time the site was entered, the type of internet browser you are using, the type of computer you are using, and the domain name of the web site from which you linked to our site. This anonymous information does not personally identify you, and is gathered by default by the web server software.

PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED  
The only personal information you will be asked to supply is your email address and a choice of username while creating a log-in account. Your personal information is stored on secure servers that are not accessible by third parties. Personally identifiable information is not viewable by other GunBot users. Billing information is handled by a third party payment processor and is not stored on our servers.

SHARING INFORMATION  
The personal information you provide will not be shared, sold or marketed to any third parties. We do not anticipate that your personal information will be shared or divulged to any third parties by us, provided such disclosure may be necessary to: (a) comply with a court order or other legal process or other legal requirements of any governmental authorities; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Gunbot.net.

CHANGES TO PRIVACY STATEMENT  
We reserve the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, change, update, or modify this Privacy Policy simply by posting such change, update or modification on the web site. Any such change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the web site.

COOKIE POLICY  
Gunbot.net uses cookies to be reminded of who you are and to help us access your account information (stored on our computers) and to deliver to you a better and more personalized service. This cookie is set when you "Log In" or make changes to forms and is erased when you "Log Out" of our web site or your browser session expires. Other third parties, beyond our control, may use cookies in other ways not yet described or thought of at this time. We take no legal responsibility for such use.
